<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Earlyrain Studio]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Earlyrain Studio]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/earlyrain-studio/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:37:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/earlyrain-studio/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Hi! I’m Chris!  If you would
have told me twenty years ago that I was going to be an artist and a landscape photographer
as my day job, I would have looked at you sideways. I am a self-taught
painter and image engineer – a closet painter for over 30 years and taking
photographs for over 40… I can’t believe that it’s been that long. My passion
for both has grown one day at a time. Every moment that I spend in the field sketching,
painting or shooting, I consider a blessing. The pace of daily life fades to
black and the Lord’s amazing creation takes center stage. I focus on creating
images that have photographic authenticity… Photos that evoke a sense of wonder
and paintings that make you want to step into the canvas. I have my beautiful
wife Naomi that supports my effort to be the best I can in my work and in
my life. I have my wonderful children that I am thankful proud of… and I have
my Lord with whom I walk every day. What more do I need?</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/earlyrain-studio/a31c8166-5d24-4664-8bee-65ba506d660a/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a31c8166-5d24-4664-8bee-65ba506d660a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Light is a language! I like to explore
the use of longer exposures to create desired dramatic or subtle effects in
water, sky or atmospheric perspective. To achieve the drama within the shot, I may use various neutral density filters and/or graduated filters to control the way light resists time. I prefer to shoot when the light and conditions are at their
best. The golden hour. The results are a great reward or frustration depending on what’s thrown at you, weather and time, the land or my endurance... HDR is OK too when the bear is at your ankles. ;)</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/earlyrain-studio/dd95e5bd-67ce-490e-b41b-b09ca3bbcbc9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dd95e5bd-67ce-490e-b41b-b09ca3bbcbc9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:06:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/74f09bc0-4a91-4bb1-93d2-aa1cdb0658e1.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/earlyrain-studio/9e75b15e-c2c6-4a62-a3de-777214e07f70/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9e75b15e-c2c6-4a62-a3de-777214e07f70</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 18:21:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>